# **Houba Vincent**

I am a fullstack developer with equal knowledge on the front and backend side.

I am a quick learner, I worked with a lot technologies, lanuages, library, frameworks.

I can make static website, spa, mobile application, cli,

rest api, work with sql and no-sql, experience in cloud

I am an expert in python (django, flask, aiohttp) and javascript (react, vue)

I Have some knowledge in data analyse and machine learning, good knowdlege of the scientific stack in python I am familiar with docker, kubernetes, linux as a developer, I could fill a dev ops but I am mostly a developer I am also a lisp hacker, emacs guru and a git ninja

# Experience

Front end engineering - (Robovision) - (June 2018 - April 2019) - (Belgium/Ghent)

- Create tools with vuejs to labeling images and add metadata to images
- Build charts and metrics in vuejs ot visualise the result of trained models on labeled images
- Upgrade and reorganise quasar (vue framework) version to more recent one
- Create reusable components (tables, modal box) in vuejs.
- Build an admin to create projects, users, groups...
- Integration test with cypress
- Python, Vue, Vuex, Vue-router, Quasar, Typescript, Es6, cypress, Docker

Full Stack Developer - (Factory) - (Aout 2017 - May 2018) - (Belgium/Liege)

#### P-heal

- Working IOT device to remind people to take their medecine.
- Create a mobile application with react-native for the IOT device.
- Build a small mvp with serverless framework in aws with dynamodb as backend and lambda function.

#### **Big Data Media**

- Create a recommendation engine for a media broadcaster.
- Build multyle microservices in python, (flask and kafka) to extract, enrich content from article, sound and video.
- Test the recommendation engine with unitetest and behave.
- Searching for solution to improve the recommendation engine (tf/idf, elasticsearch).
- Create a cache system with redis to avoid collecting and fetching the same data.
- Collect data on users (time spended on article, time spend watching a video...) to rate articles and videos.
- Python, kafka, aiohttp, sql, behave, unittest, react, docker, redis, pyspark, pandas

#### **Doctena**

- Make their eamils responsive with ljml
- Improve javascript code with angular and jquery
- Work on visual bugfix, Make the application responsive and improve the croos browser compatibilities

#### Logdirect

- Refactor front end code for different site, with jquery, gulp, css
- Unittest made home framework with nodejs

#### atHome

Bulding static analyse tools with typescript (made home framework)

### Education

### Aug 2015-May 2016

Java cloud computing; STE-Formations(Liege)

- Learning advanced design pattern in java
- Algorithm course on paper
- database analyse and creation
- Advanced sql with postgresql (view, trigger, creating function) psql
- Building a sudoku

### Aug 2012-May 2015

Bac Web developer; IPSF(Liege)

- Learning html, css, jquery, php, mysql, wordpress (first year)
- learning poo, symfony2, version control (second year)
- Building website for asbl in symfony2 (second year)
- Creating a site for lawfirm with python(django) (final)

## Skills

- Languages:
  - Python 5
  - Javascript (es6) 4
  - Typescript 3
  - Ruby 3
  - Bash 2
  - Node 2
  - Elisp 2
  - Elixir 2
  - Clojure 2
  - Php 1
  - Java 1
- Framework python:

- Django 3
- Flask 3
- Nikola 2
- Aiohttp 1

### • Framework javascript:

- Vue 4
- Quasar 4
- React 3
- Redux 3
- React native 3
- Gatsby 3
- Jquery 2
- Angular 2

### • Integrations:

- Css 3
- Stylus 3
- Bulma 3
- Sass 2
- Foundation 2
- Bootstrap 2
- Materialize 2

### • Build tools:

- Webapck 3
- Brunch 2
- Gulp 2
- Grunt 2

#### • Servers:

- Nginx 2
- Apache 2

### • Databases:

- Postgresql 3
- Mysql 2
- Sqlite 2
- Mongo 2
- Redis 3
- Dynamodb 3

#### Tools:

- Emacs 5
- Git 4
- Aws 3
- Docker 3
- Google cloud 2
- Vagrant 2
- Jira 2
- Gitlab 3
- Github 2
- Bitbucket 2

- Jenkins 2
- Os:
  - Ubuntu 3
  - Debian 3
  - Arch 3
  - Redhat 1

# Extra

- Languages:
  - French (native speaker)
  - English (excellent)
- hobbies
  - Webscraping, Machine learning, Data analyst, Game creation
  - Science, Reading, History,
  - documentaries

houbavince@gmail.com • +32499316385 • 29 years old Liege, Belgium (open to relocation) Website: https://mindfullcoder